2.0.1
=====
694		Fixed: wflow-wfweb - Show a more relevant message when exporting a Userview (#127) 
693		Fixed: Designer - Have Workflow Designer report actual error while trying to upload (#89)
689		Fixed: WfWeb - SET variable button in Completed Activity is not disabled (#160)
688		Added: Bean Shell Plugin - Included form package to support form api
686		Fixed: wflow-wfweb -JSON API Authentication - j_username is insignificant (#162)
685		Modified: Bean shell plugin - Add hash variable support for form variable plugin type & participant plugin type.
684		Fixed: wflow-formsweb - Form Builder - File type and file name of the uploaded file not correctly set in output stream (#151)
683		Fixed: Form - Form Data Table Column Not Automatically Created (#148)
682		Fixed: Userview - Can't Create Too Many Categories (#156)
681		Modified: wflow-form - JSON API - NPE thrown when web/json/workflow/assignment/complete/ is used in a process that contains workflow variable (#149)
679		Userview: JavaScript error when setting category permissions (#152)
678		Fixed: Userview - Can't Create Too Many Categories (#156)
677		Fixed: Service Level Report - Deleted package still listed in the process definition filter (#150)
676		Fixed: Form - Commented unnecessary check for grid (#147)
675		Fixed: WfWeb - Prevent JavaScript error "loginCallback is not defined" when logging into the embedded inbox.
674		Modified: Directory - Removed unused dependency to spring-ldap.
672		Modified: Wfweb - JSON API Login to use DirectoryManager's authentication method as well to handle hashed login r669
671		Fixed: WfWeb - jQuery selector scoping does not work properly in IE7 (issue #141)
670		Fixed: Form - Proper close of Hibernate session (#142)
669		Enhanced: Directory - AssignmentManager.login accepts hashed login in the password parameter for security enhancement (#143)
668		Fixed: WfWeb - Process start white list does not move on to next version properly (#144)
667		Fixed: WfWeb - added username and hash parameter to launch workflow designer in process update view
666		Enhanced: WfWeb/Designer - secured package deploy & update json api to prevent unauthenticated access (issue #139)
665		Fixed: Task History - Hash variable not parsed (#136) 
		Fixed: Monitor Processes - Column for Run Process Performer (Requestor) (#135)
664		Fixed: Wfweb - PO File import - Populate locale filter dropdown list after importing a PO File (issue #138)
663		Fixed: Form Builder - Unicode characters not working when uploading a file in Form Builder (#137).
662		Fixed: WfWeb - Prevent NullPointerException when starting a process without additional request parameters, from r658.
661		Fixed: Form Facade - fixed code to retrieve worklfow variable even if there is no submitted form data
660		Fixed: Form - Subform loading error
659		Fixed: Form - Some Hash Variables Not Working in Form Attached to Run Process (#125)
658		Fixed: WfWeb / Form Builder - possible XSS entry points (issue #133)
657		Modified: General - Modified POMs to allow building of project without access to SVN.
656		Modified: Database Plugin / MySQL Plugin - Modified POM to remove redundant jdbc-stdext dependency
655		Added: JSON Plugin - Imported java OSGI package for javax.net, javax.net.ssl (#131)
654		Fixed: Form Variable - Can't configure plugin, when runtime exception caught (#132)
653		Added: Bean Shell Plugin - Imported OSGI package for Oracle JDBC connection (#130)
652		Fixed: Form Builder - The saved value of form variable element is not selected in sub-form (#129)


2.0.0
=====		
639		Fixed: MySQL Plugin - escape backslash (issue #108)
638		Fixed: Database Plugin - escape backslash (issue #108)
637		Modified: Form Builder / Form Variable - Increased form variable table column width to 300px for better viewing.
636		Modified: User Notification Plugin - Don't attempt to send email when the SMTP host is not set, and removed unnecessary log messages.
635		Fixed: Form Builder - Irrelevant properties for Read-Only Text Field and Read-Only Text Area (#114)
633		Fixed: wfDirectory - Grade list is not loaded correctly when edit user (#116) 
		Modified: wfDirectory - Add validation to prevent same orgranization id and name.
632		Enhanced: MySQL Plugin - Added Extra Parameters attribute for greater control.
631		Modified: wfWeb - Disabled sorting of 'Version' column in view form category page
630		Fixed: Import/Export - form variables are imported but not working in form (#106)
629		Fixed: Form Builder - Irrelevant properties for Read-Only Text Field and Read-Only Text Area (#114)
628		Fixed: Database Plugin - Fixed JDBC update not working in SQL Server.
627		Modified: Directory - Added Grade Name in View User page. Moved position of Emploment Role up to after Employment Code in Edit User page. #112
626		Fixed: Database Plugin - Fixed hash variable value containing single quotes (') not working in r621 (#108)
625		Added: Import/Export - form variables included (issue #106)
624		Fixed: wfWeb - Group deletion for forms - correct language (#111) 
		Fixed: wfWeb - Two confusing 'delete' buttons on the Form Category page (#110)
623		Fixed: MySQl/ Database Plugin - Typo correction of r621 (When hash variable value contain single quotes ('), it break the query.)
621		Fixed: MySQl/ Database Plugin - When hash variable value contain single quotes ('), it break the query. (#108)
620		Fixed: userview - Input checking during new Userview creation removes all other field inputs when there's an error. (#109)
618		Fixed: wfWeb/ wfForm - Editable label show '<', '>' and '&' as escape character when in editing mode.
617		Fixed: Directory - Removal of user(s) in bulk #71
615		Modified: Community Plugins - Updated description as in #96
614		Fixed: Import/Export - Added additional null checking for userview categories when importing a userview.
612		Added: wfWeb - Added delete selection of Forms (#69)
611		Added: WfWeb - show master login hash in system setup list
610		Fixed: Import/Export - subform not being exported (issue #102)
609		Added: wfWeb - Add Delete button under Edit Userview page (#103)
608		Modified: Userview - Sorted list of process definitions by process name.
607		Modified: WfEngine - Sorted list of package definitions by package name.
606		Modified: SLA - Sorted drop-down list of process definitions by process name.
605		Modified: Form Builder - Increased textarea height in the form builder to 150px.
604		Fixed: Userview - Fixed NullPointerException when a userview activity is mapped to a missing form.
603		Modified: WfWeb - Hide "Show Additional Info" in the start process and assignment view when the "embed=true" URL parameter is used. (#100)
602		Fixed: wfWeb - Correction of label & error message
601		Fixed: wfWeb - Deleting form does not remove mapping in process. (#94) 
		Fixed: Form - Form hang when subform not exist.
599		Fixed: Import/Export - form mapped to Userview activity not being exported (issue #92) 
		Fixed: Import/Export - version of the form mapped to Userview activity not being updated correctly (issue #70)
598		Fixed: Directory - Remove user's employment properly when user's org id is blank when editing user in User Setup as reported in #71 (To fix r594 unsolved issue)
597		Added: WfWeb - Added optional parentProcessId parameter in /web/client/process/start JSON API to allow linking with a parent process.
596		Fixed: Form Builder - Irrelevant properties for HTML Editor.(#82) Fixed: Form Builder - Properties value of HTML Editor are not show in Edit Advanced Property Dialog. 
595		Fixed: Designer - Package Id is editable when updating an existing process.(#80) 
		Fixed: Designer - New process not able to deploy when launch designer in update mode.
594		Fixed: Directory - Remove user's employment properly when user's org id is blank when editing user in User Setup as reported in #71
593		Fixed: Form Builder - Put curly bracket with word in form builder will automaticaly replace to 'undefied' when display. eg: '{ c u r l y b r a c k e t s }' (#93)
592		Fixed: Form Builder - Irrelevant properties shown when edit Advanced Properties of a row (#82)
591		Fixed: wfWeb - Correction of validation message
590		Fixed: Directory - Typo in resources property file for issue #87. "Password dismatch" -> "Password mismatch"
589		Fixed: Hash Variable - cannot be processed for certain non-alphanumeric characters such as $ (issue #72) Enhanced: WfEngine - added option for custom-defined string replace in WorkflowUtil.processVariable()
588		Fixed: wfWeb - Error when ProcessDefId contain period(.) (#77)
587		Fixed: wfDirectory - Error when username contain special char (#85)
586		Fixed: wfDirectory - Error when department code, grade code, group code or organization code contain special char (#86)
585		Fixed: Form - NullPointerException when the form variable does not exist
584		Fixed: wfEngine - SLA report shows incorrect min and max delay values (#90)
583		Fixed: Userview - Id does not validate for non-alphanumeric characters. (#78)
582		Modified: MySQL Plugin - Updated plugin getDescription() message.
581		Modified: Versioning in mysql plugin and added plugin into wflow-plugins's pom.xml
579		Modified: Designer - Modified startup image and icon for the designer.
576		Fixed: Form - Form ID does not validate for non-alphanumeric characters. Fixed: Form - Form table names should also be restricted to 28 characters (to cater to the default Oracle name limit) (issue #73)
575		Fixed: Directory - Adding new sub-department missing hidden fields error #67
574		Fixed: Directory - Remove user's subordinates relation when removing a user. #66
572		Fixed: Userview - Error when process name & activity name contain apostrophe(') (Issue #61) 
		Fixed: Userview - Error when column label contain comma(,), colon(:), apostrophe('), close square bracket(]) and hash(#). (Issues #62 #81 #88) 
		Fixed: Userview - Error when category contain comma(,) and colon(:). (Issue #83)
571		Modified: WfInstall - Modified installation bundle for Linux to place all directories and files within a directory named joget-linux-${project.version}
569		Fixed: WfWeb - Login for embedded inbox not working correctly.
568		Modified: WfEngine - Avoid starting a process when copying from another instance, and refactored process starting code.
567		Fixed: WfEngine / WfWeb - Fixed workflow variable not being set by a submitted form from a linked process.
566		Refactored: WfEngine / Form / WfWeb - Refactored processStart methods to return a WorkflowProcessResult object instead of a String.
565		Modified: Directory - Modified user HOD check for reporting structure compatibility to recursively lookup parent departments until a matching HOD is found.
564		Fixed: Directory / WfWeb - Incorrect link to subdepartment view page, and show parent department where available.
563		Added: WfEngine / WfWeb - Added experimental features to start any activity in a running process, and to start a new process by copying from a running process instance.
562		Added: WfWeb - resource bundle message for read-only textarea
561		Added: Form Builder - read-only text area Modified: Form Builder - hide fieldset in subform if the fieldset contains only subform
560		Fixed: Wfweb : Redirect to the newly created form when selecting an existing form to be copied from.
559		Fixed: Form : Form list not showing when selecting form to be copied from when adding new form.
558		Fixed: WfWeb - Value of "Show The Next Assignment When Completed" not saved into new version (issue #54)
557		Modified: WfEngine - Added check for running state when aborting activities.
556		Added: WfWeb - Added JSON API to abort running activities by process instance ID and activity definition ID.
555		Enhanced: WfWeb - Added name filter for user selection when reassigning a running activity.
554		Added: Settings - Added feature to import PO File.

2.0-beta 3
==========
548		Fixed: Mobile - Removed hardcoded context path for mobile form submission.
547		Modified: Form/WfEngine/WfWeb - modified run process with form to only create process instance after form submission r526 r538; reduced the number of ajax calls when starting a process
545		Fixed: Form Builder - Uploaded Chinese file cannot load correctly in form
543		Modified: WfWeb - Excluded the show next assignment checkbox for tool
541		Added: WfEngine - method to abort all activity instances based on activity definition id & process instance id
540		Enhanced: Designer - Display activity limits in the graph if specified.
539		Enhanced: Designer - Automatically increase activity box size (up to a 150px) to fit longer text labels.
538		Enhanced: Mobile - Save mobile form data of run process form before start the process. Enhanced: Mobile - Workflow Variable in run process mobile form now can be set.
537		Fixed: WfWeb - Fixed for r535 : value of show next assignment not loading correctly. Added: Import/Export - Included activity setup in import/export package
536		Fixed: WfWeb - possible NullPointerException when viewing a form (issue #48)
535		Modified: WfWeb - Uncomment the code for r477 (Commented out "Subsequent assignments to continue showing if assigned to the same user"); Fixed: WfWeb - Subsequent assignments to continue showing not working when no form but having workflow variable; Added: WfWeb - Added configuration on update process page for continue showing subsequent assignments
534		Enhanced: Userview - Not showing start process link if user is not in whitelist.
533		Modified: Designer - Display version and build number in the Workflow Designer window title.
532		Modified: Designer - Modified default transition style to Orthogonal.
531		Fixed: Designer - Fixed Spline and Bezier transition styles not working when selected.
530		Fixed: Form Builder - formbuilder.template.js to continue with error in case there is a regex conflict (issue #47)
529		Fixed: Form Builder - issue #39 Error in forms when fields have the same name with different case.
528		Added: Userview - 'refName' system column in activity setup's column selection.
526		Enhanced: WfWeb - Save form data of run process form before start the process; Enhanced: WfWeb - Workflow Variable in run process form now can be set; Modified: WfWeb - Disable 'External Form' tab when add/edit form mapping of 'Run Process' 
525		Fixed: Import/Export - exception thrown when exporting process with same form mapped to multiple activities
524		Fixed: Userview - Prevent NullPointerException when an activity is mapped to a form that does not exist.
522		Fixed: WfWeb - added anonymous permission for /web/formbuilder/getFormVariable
521		Fixed: Form Builder - elements with form variable do not get pre-selected with submitted data 
520		Fixed: Userview - Prevent NullPointerException when a category is mapped to a group that does not exist.
517		Enhanced: Userview - Ability to append item into activity group permission.
516		Enhanced: WfWeb - added name filter for user assignment in group view, group assignment in user view Fixed: WfWeb - incorrect column labels
515		Enhanced: Directory - added name filter for UserDao.getAssignUsers(), UserDao.getUnAssignUsers(), GroupDao.getAssignGroups() & GroupDao.getUnAssignGroups()
514		Modified: Userview - Rename "Save" button to "Done" in edit activity popup. Modified: Form Builder - Rename "Save" button to "Done" in edit advanced property.

2.0-beta-2
==========
507		Added: WfInstall - Added wflowdb-sample.sql which contains the sample userview and organization data.
506		Fixed: WfInstall - Updated wflowdb-empty.sql to the minimum required data with case sensitive table names.
505		Fixed: Monitoring - Graph cannot be generated due to NullPointerException when the XPDL content contains an ampersand (&)
504		Modified: Form Builder - Disable ENTER key when filling in a form to prevent submission and showing {success:true}
498		Modified: WfWeb - Show process started message if next acivity after process started is not belong to the current user
497		Fixed: Userview - Newly added activity does not follow the category permission
496		Fixed: Userview - Hash Variable of Activity Name is not show correctly in Inbox
495		Modified: WfWeb - Added link back to the main page in the 404 error page.
494		Modified: WfWeb - Redirect to process listing page instead of showing exception if process definition ID is not available.
493		Enhanced: WfWeb - added name filter for group list & user list in process whitelist mapping & userview category permission
492		Enhanced: DirectoryManager - added name filter for getGroupList() & getUserList()
		Enhanced: WfWeb - added name filter for group list & user list in participant mapping
491		Enhanced: Userview - To only show "Form saved" after page loaded completely. Page does not refresh by itself also.
490		Fixed: WfWeb - Complete button in assignment form was disabled after validation fail (Fixed for r456)
489		Modified: Form Builder -  Allow "advanced properties" to be closed by pressing Esc key 
488		Modified: WfWeb -  When creating a new form from View Form Category, the Category selectbox should default its value to the category I'm viewing
487		Fixed: Userview: Removal of columns in userview activity setup.
486		Modified: PluginManager - Improved Felix container shutdown method
485		Enhanced: WfEngine - Added additional hash variable types #user.username.attribute# and #uservariable.variableName.userAttribute#
483		Fixed: Form Builder - Workflow Variable of Hash variable cannot show correctly in form. 
482		Fixed: WfWeb - NullPointerException when a field with workflow variable submitted with empty value.
481		Added: Wfweb - Embedded code for process list view and inbox.
480		Fixed: Form Builder - Properties of checkbox and radio button not correctly set when creating a new checkbox or radio button option.
479		Modified: WfEngine - Added additional condition to prevent possible NullPointerException when disconnecting.
478		Fixed: Form Builder - Grid data is copy over from default row to new row when add a new row in IE
476		Fixed: formbuilder - Delete icon of grid is still showing when a subform is disabled.
474		Fixed: formbuilder - Extra rows was added to grid in a subform
473		Fixed: Userview - changed to replaceAll() instead of replace() for r472
472		Fixed: Userview - javascript error when there is a single quote in column label
469		Fixed: formbuilder - Disable subform not working
468		Modified: XPDL Image - Added additional code synchronization to prevent exceptions when generating images concurrently.
467		Added: WfWeb - RSS for Inbox
466		Fixed: XPDL Image - Fixed image not being generated in the background when deploying or updating a process.
465		Fixed: WfWeb - Validation of "Table Name" field when create new form not working.
		Fixed: WfWeb - Autocomplete of "Table Name" field not working in IE.
464		Fixed: EmailPlugin - Log message not showing the correct sender address when sending email.
462		Fixed: Json Table - Javascript error when having button without enable checkbox or radio button.
461		Added: WfWeb - Master username & master password hashing for JSON API
		Modified: WfWeb - Revamp authenticate method in WorkflowHttpAuthProcessingFilter
		Modified: StringUtil - moved md5 generator to StringUtil
		Added: WfDirectory - Added login Hash generator for user object based on username and password
460		Enhanced: Email Plugin - Support send email by using multiple participant IDs in "To (participant ID)"
458		Enhanced: WfWeb - Pass current URL Parameters to the next assignment view when continuelly show subsequent assignments
456		Fixed: WfWeb - Callback after complete assignment does not work.
452		Enhanced: PluginManager - Detect existing cache directories for bundles to prevent conflicts between running instances, added info logging for started bundles, and better exception handling to catch more general exceptions.
450		Enhanced: Directory - Added Ajax effect - Not to refresh page when a user/group is removed from the participant mapping.
449		Modified: General - Removed hardcoded skipTests configuration in POMs so that tests can be skipped if required.
448		Fixed: WfWeb - reduced unnecessary logging when authenticating user
447		Added: UI - Added "Run Process" button in Process Configuration View 
444		Fixed: Database Resource Bundle - Exclusion EHCACHE from hibernate dependancy because a newer version is used
442		Fixed: Form mapping - Include missing existing external url and its iframe CSS in form activity mapping.
441		Enhanced: Database Resource Bundle - Improve preformance by using EHCACHE
440		Added: WfWeb - username & password hashing for JSON API
436		Enhanced: Directory - Individual removal feature for each user/group in participant mapping.
434		Enhanced: Directory - Append any new user or group to existing mapping.
431		Enhancement: Designer - Show up the package's properties automatically when a new package is created.
430		Modified: Import Export - Changed the import message and css of the message
428		Enhancement: Userview - Ability to customize all the 4 buttons labels in admin panel and ability to show/hide Cancel and Withdraw buttons for tasks selected from category list.
426		Fixed: UI - Radio in Json table not working after the modification to allow checkbox selection across pages.
425		Modified: UI - Changed popup message when update process via workflow designer 
424		Fixed: wfEngine - Form mapped to run process failed to load.
422		Fixed: UI - Checkboxs in Json table are not able tick for multiple pages. 
420		Fixed: Form Builder - Sub Form is missing when save
419		Modified: ImportExportManager - Remove unnecessary missing message
417		Fixed: Plugin Configuration - Plugin hard coded default value cannot show in checkbox, radio button and select box 
416		Modified: WfWeb - Set response content type to image/jpeg when displaying process XPDL thumbnails and images.
415		Enhanced: UI - Group system setting with subheader.
414		Fixed: Userview - moved specific css style back to userviewCreateSelectActivity.jsp
413		Fixed: Userview - Incorrect css problem.
412		Modified: wfDesigner - Hide unused toolbar icons.
411		Enhanced: WfEngine - copy mobile form when updating a process
410		Fixed: Import/Export - mobile form doesn't get exported properly when there are multiple processes in one package
409		Fixed: UI - Right to left not working in userview login page.
		Fixed: Userview - Custom layout not working in userview login page.
408		Modified: Userview - Option to start process automatically without showing 'run' button.
407		Enhanced: UI - RTL support in form builder
406		Modified: WfEngine - Modified JPEG image generation to use JDK ImageIO instead of proprietary Sun classes.
405		Modified: DesignerWeb - Modified JPEG image generation to use JDK ImageIO, removed redundant custom encoding classes.
404		Enhanced: UI - RTL support in form builder
403		Enhanced: UI - RTL support in WMC & userview
402		Added: Import/Export - mobile form support
401		Fixed: WfEngine - Fixed process definitions being loaded from cache when switching profiles or when accessing a different virtual host.
400		Added: WfEngine - interception point for a deadline plugin
399		Enhanced: UI - RTL support in userview
398		Enhanced: UI - RTL support in WMC
396		Enhancement: Designer - Create new package and shows its properties automatically when Designer is launched.
395		Modified: UI - Minor grammar correction on the prompt to go to the latest process version when updating via designer.
392		Enhancement: Designer - Added Undo/Redo button on the toolbar.
391		Fixed: Userview - ProcessStartWhiteList is checked in the process list in add/edit userview activity
		Added: Wflow - Support start process with latest process def id
		Enhanced: UI - Show message to go latest process configuration view when click update via designer
390		Modified: WfWeb - Prevent thread from waiting during Tomcat shutdown by using a context listener to stop Felix in PluginManager.
388		Fixed: Form - Date Picker icon not loading correctly in Sub Form because of Sub Form child controls not have unique id.

2.0-beta-1
==========
376		Added: Mobile Form
373		Added: Userview
372		Enhanced: UI - New user interface
370		Added: XPDL image in update process view
369		Fixed: Form - Readonly text field width is not consistant with text field
361		Fixed: Import/Export - Fixed form ID version inconsistency. Previously the newly imported form maintain the original version number in its ID rather than using the latest version in the current database.
356		Fixed: UI - Text Field in plugin configuration page not able to show value with double quotes.
343		Fixed: Directory - Added missing timezone list after hitting error in user profile update.
341		Fixed: Directory - Added missing organization attribute after the form hit error when user tries to insert new department under a organization.
339		Fixed: Directory - Fixed bug whereby user can't change the edit profile parameter to hack into other user's account. User will now able to edit their own account's details only.
337		Added: Form Builder - Hash variable support
336		Fixed: WfDirectory - Fixed bug whereby user can't change the edit profile parameter to hack into other user's account. User will now able to edit their own account's details only.
335		Fixed: Import/Export - Cannot export when map participant to previous activity
331		Fixed: Plugin - Plugin Configuration page cannot show the default value that come with plugin in textarea.
329		Fixed: WfDirectory - Department list under org shows only parent departments. Problem with JSON controller retrieval as it fethes all records then only filter the parent out. Will show all departments and show its parent department now.
328		Added: Form View UI - parent form list and workflow activity list
326		Fixed: WfDirectory - NullPointerException when the user does not belong to any department in getUserSubordinate()
325		Enhanced: UI - Show available table name when create form.
322		Enhanced: UI - All reference name/id are linked to its own page.
		Enhanced: UI - Show package name by default at update process page.
312		Fixed: WfDesigner - default <xpdl:Script> tag not being created upon creating a new package

1.1.3
=====
292		Fixed: WfDirectory - getUserSubordinate() doesn't include department users
290		Fixed: WfDirectory - "report to" doesn't work properly
288		Modified: Version - Changed the Version changes list to read from http://www.joget.org/updates/changes
285		Added: UI - login page welcome message bubble
		Added: UI - get help link on sidebar
283		Enhance: Form - Added validation for element name.
281		Fixed: Form - Custom input validation not working.
265		Fixed: Form - Date picker still showing calendar icon when it is disabled
233		Modified: WfEngine - Modified assignment listing and size to allow optional parameters to filter by process definition ID and process instance ID
232		Fixed: WfEngine - Fixed non-editable workflow variables not being processed as a hash variable
231		Modified: WfEngine - Optimized performance of assignment listing by removing unnecessary calls
209		Fixed: Form - Datepicker's icon still showing after form overlay
199		Fixed: Form - Anonymous not able to view start process

1.1.2
=====
144		Fixed: Workflow Engine - Process Start White List(Participant mapping) mapping is lost, every time when a process is updated
143		Fixed: Form Builder - Subform is still enabled, even when it's set as disabled
142		Fixed: Design Processes - Package import/export doesn't include external form mapping CSS style
141		Enhanced: org.joget.directory.model.service.DirectoryManagerImpl - Enhanced with extra conditional checks to prevent NullPointerException when department or HOD is not available

1.1.1
=====
118		Modified: org.joget.workflow.model.service.WorkflowManagerImpl - Modified implementation of getProcessVariable method
117		Modified: JSON API - Modified implementation of /json/workflow/variable/list/

1.1.0
=====
106		Fixed: Form Builder - Invalid/duplicated row ID problem (row_id of subform not properly passed)
105		Added: Form Builder - JavaScript alert message to show that a form has been saved, after clicking on "Save" button
104		Modified: Form Builder - Reduced the font size to 9pt for HTML Editor.
102		Fixed: Form Builder - HTML Editor has data saving/loading issue
98		Fixed: Form Builder - HTML Editor is not working properly in form view
97		Fixed: Form Builder - Radio button, check box and select box's key value is shown in its label in mobile view 
								Empty label not editable after saving the form
								Hidden field element disappear after saving the form
96		Modified: Form Builder - Increased year range of date picker to +/- 100 years
94		Added: External Form - Support for CSS style for external form IFrame in assignmentEmbeddedView
90		Added: Form Builder - formbuilderOnSubmitSuccess() and formbuilderOnValidationFailed() custom JavaScript events
90		Fixed: Form Builder - The "loading" message dispalyed when Form Builder is initializing, doesn't support i18n
89		Modified: Workflow Enfine - Changed the way of setting a process variable in processVariable().
									Changed the sequence of setting variable(s) upon starting a process.
									Changed Shark.conf to use process context when evaluating deadlines.
88		Enhanced: Form Builder - Better i18n support by loading message resource bundle from Java properties file instead of JavaScript
85		Fixed: Reference ID Plugin - Database column "created" is null, when a new row is inserted into the form data table
83		Removed: Windows Installer - Save selected language into Registry
82		Removed: Email Plugin - "Participant Type" field
80		Enhanced: Plugins - To display default property values in plugin configuration screen (while mapping an activity to a plugin)
78		Added: org.joget.workflow.model.service.WorkflowManager - Overload the processStart method to support starting a process by specific user
77		Refactored: Deleted unused folders and classes from wflow-plugin-base
76		Refactored: Moved classes related to the Default Plugin Properties feature from wflow-plugin-base to wflow-wfengine
75		Enhanced: Hash Variable - To support addition/substraction of Day/Month/Year to current date for #date# Hash Variable (#date.[DAY/MONTH/YEAR][+/-]IntegerValue.java_SimpleDateFormat#)
74		Added: Plugins - Support configuration of default properties for form variable, application and participant plugins, in Settings > Manage Plugins.
73		Enhanced: Workflow Designer - To support the locale setting configured in Workflow Management Console (Settings > System Setup)
72		Modified: Workflow Designer - Changed default name of Route element to "Route" (previously was "Activity")
71		Added: Windows Installer - To support multiple-language selection
70		Enhanced: i18n - Get message resource bundle from both database and properties file, for all locales. Before this, database was the only supported message resource bundle source for locale other than en_US.
69		Removed: Email Plugin - "To (participant ID)" and "Participant ID Type" fields
68		Enhanced: Email Plugin - To support Hash Variable in "CC" field
66		Enhanced: Email Plugin - To support auto-retrieval of email address by username, in "To (specific email address)" and "CC" field
65		Enhanced: Email Plugin - Use directoryManager to get user's email instead of using userDao
64		Enhanced: BeanShell Plugin - To support Hash Variable in the script, when it's used as application plugin
63		Enhanced: Workflow Management Console - New "Start Process" screen
61		Enhanced: JSON Plugin - Set formatted output to workflow variable
60		Enhanced: Hash Variable - Deprecate #performer.activityDefId# and expand the scope to #performer.activityDefId.propertyName#
58		Added: Hash Variable - Support for #performer.activityDefId# to get performer's user ID of an activity instance in a process instance using activity definition ID
54		Added: Form Builder - disableChildControl property to grid, to separate "Disable" control of grid from its child element
53		Enhanced: Email Plugin - Add support for multiple recipient email addresses in the "To (specific email address)" field, and to support Hash Variables in the "From" field. Semicolon can now be used as the email delimiter as an alternative to comma.
52		Fixed: Form Builder - Add and remove controls of selectbox are shown in subform's grid
50		Fixed: Form Builder - When passing "overlay=true" to the formbuilder url, everything within that page will be disabled. Resolved by only applying overlay on elements inside formbuilder_main div
49		Fixed: Form Builder - If using 2 selectboxes in a grid, the 2nd selectbox's functions (add and remove options) will refer to the 1st selectbox. This means, when I click on "Add" for the 2nd selectbox, the new entry will be reflected on the 1st
48		Modified: Joget Form - Ignore form field validation when saving a form as draft
46		Enhanced: Form Builder - If a new category is created in the Create Form screen, by default, the just-created category will be set as the selected category for the form you're creating
45		Added: Form Builder - "Copy form from" feature in Create New Form
43		Fixed: jsonTable - Alignment issue when single-select mode is activated. Resolved by adding a disabled radio button to jsontable header
42		Fixed: jsonTable - Parent form submitted when a button is clicked. Resolved by adding type="button" attribute to jsonTable buttons
39		Fixed: Form Builder - Controls of add and remove element are shown in subform
39		Enhanced: Form Builder - New dialog-box to help users to setup value-label pairs for select box, check box and radio button.
38		Fixed: Design Processes - After updating/removing mapping for a process, it doesn't correctly return to the selected tab in Process Configuration
34		Modified: Moved escapeRegex(inStr:String) method from JsonPlugin to StringUtil
33		Fixed: Workflow Management Console - CSS font-size property for the sub-menu in main tab is incorrectly set to 14px
32		Fixed: Monitor Processes - "Reassign" and "Complete" buttons are shown in activity monitoring view even when the activity is of state "closed.terminated" or "closed.aborted"
22		Fixed: org.joget.workflow.model.WorkflowFacade - "processDefId" parameter name is confused as "processId"
19		Refactored: Refactored codes to retrieve the base directory from the utility method SetupManager.getBaseDirectory()
18		Added: wflow-install - Added creation of Linux tar.gz. bundle. For that purpose, replaced ant and tomcat zip files with tar.gz files.
17		Fixed: Workflow Designer - Un-meaningful error messages shown, when there's any error thrown while updating or deploying a package
16		Added: Hash Variable - #currentUsername# Hash Variable to return the username of currently logged-on user
15		Added: org.joget.workflow.model.service.WorkflowManagerImpl - Set process version to activity when retrieving activity list
14		Added: Setup Users - Batch-delete for organization, group, grade, department, sub-department and user
12		Added: Workflow Designer - Undo/redo feature
11		Added: Monitor Processes - Batch-delete for completed processes
10		Added: Monitor Processes - Batch-delete for running processes
9		Modified: Database - Changed the date type of wf_report.assignmentUsers from varchar to text to cater for lengthier  data
7		Fixed: Design Processes - Exception thrown when exporting a package which contains external form mapping
6		Fixed: Settings - Default value of "Uploaded File Storage Base Path" in System Setup is shown as user's home directory even if wflow.home property exists